<updates>
    <update version="0.6.0">
        <files>
            <file path="Components/LiveSplit.StreamerBot.dll" status="changed" />
        </files>
        <changelog>
            <change>Fixed a case during restarting where checking game time could resolve in an unhandled exception due to CurrentSplit being null.</change>
            <change>Added fields related to Meta Data obtained from Speedrun.com, that can be specified under "Other" when editing splits. This includes elements such as leaderboard URL, subcategories, variables and platform used. Refer to wiki for more information.</change>
        </changelog>
    </update>
    <update version="0.5.0">
        <files>
            <file path="Components/LiveSplit.StreamerBot.dll" status="changed" />
        </files>
        <changelog>
            <change>Implemented test buttons (although they could be better)</change>
            <change>Implemented a new event - OnLostPBPace that runs when the time difference on a split changes from negative to positive (you end up behind the PB) - please update it on the side of StreamerBot as well!</change>
        </changelog>
    </update>
    <update version="0.4.0">
        <files>
            <file path="Components/LiveSplit.StreamerBot.dll" status="changed" />
        </files>
        <changelog>
            <change>Game name and category are now included in all requests to make it a bit easier to do conditional checks.</change>
        </changelog>
    </update>
    <update version="0.3.0">
        <files>
            <file path="Components/LiveSplit.StreamerBot.dll" status="changed" />
        </files>
        <changelog>
            <change>Replaced LostTimeOnSplit and WasLastSplitGold with SegmentResult enum.</change>
            <change>OnPause and OnResume not has the same fields as OnPauseGameTime, e.g. CurrentGameTime, CurrentRealTime and CurrentLoadTime.</change>
        </changelog>
    </update>
    <update version="0.2.0">
        <files>
            <file path="Components/LiveSplit.StreamerBot.dll" status="changed" />
        </files>
        <changelog>
            <change>Implemented LostTimeOnSplit for Split.</change>
            <change>Inverted SplitTimeDifference, so that negative is time saved and positive timespan is time lost, because that's how it is displayed in LiveSplit.</change>
            <change>Fixed disposing the component when removing it from the list of layout elements.</change>
        </changelog>
    </update>
    <update version="0.1.0">
        <files>
            <file path="Components/LiveSplit.StreamerBot.dll" status="changed" />
            <file path="Components/Newtonsoft.Json.dll" status="changed" />
        </files>
        <changelog>
            <change>Initial release</change>
        </changelog>
    </update>
</updates>